and Now ladies and gentlemen Canada's Z
and the pride of bampton
Ontario Eddie had Arena give it up
for Russell
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
hey Abu
Dhabi see fo
Habi give it up for my DJ starting from
scratch the one and
only give it up for that guy for never
giving up a buffet Give It Up
[Applause]
I mean that respectfully I
mean I mean they're called skinny jeans
is all I'm saying
um good to have white people in the
middle that's nice to see
um this is how you know the Arabs didn't
want to sit right there they're like no
please uh abat please take this seat
best seat best seat no I I love you I
want you to have I want you please enjoy
please please
um where are you guys from UK uh UK I'm
fine thank you but where are you from
um where are you from you don't like my
answer I'm from Russia you're you're
from Russia that's okay I'm not
Ukrainian it's fine you can be Russian n
of good [__]
[Applause]
and you're from the UK London good
London and you Dubai Dubai no that's
what I thought when I looked at you
yeah look like a bootleg Dubai um maybe
like the Kurama version of Dubai I don't
know and what's your name Russian guy
your name Tim Tim Tim
Tim Tim Timor Timor I actually also from
Dubai but I know I know you all think
you're from Dubai but um if you don't
have an amarati passport you're just
visiting like the rest of us
[Applause]
um what are you doing out here Tim what
what made you invade I mean
uh come come
here here I'm laugh having a good time
you're having a good time you living out
here or you you live out here is your
hearing
bad were you on the warfront and the
[__] explosions got to
you
[Music]
boom bless I don't know what
you do you know that brown kid beside
you
that one there do you know
him just checking I mean I mean it's
Dubai everybody owns an Indian somehow I
don't know we all look at
there I don't know if there was a group
on or something
but well it's nice to see white people
um at least you know and then people in
white um
[Applause]
I don't like the term I want to let you
guys know what's your name English guy
Martin Martin right
um be honest with you Martin you sound
like a bit of a [__]
um I say it with respect mate all right
and who's the ginger Bastard with you
[Applause]
um hey the big guy like thank God the
heat's off me
uh it's better to get it first then the
rest of them take it after you know what
I
mean my boss it's your boss oh nice are
you the boss he's like I don't ENT
anything either are you Arab sir no what
are you from Pakistan I Liv in you're
from Pakistan so you're Indian
[Applause]
um listen if you did some DNA
tracing
Sur I don't like the term white people
Martin that's what I was trying to say
I'll tell you why I don't like the term
white people because you hear white
people you automatically assume color
and that's just not the case with white
anybody could be physically white really
anybody like you can go to India and go
to the north and you'll meet a guy with
white skin and blue eyes you like you
white he like not even a tiny
bit like White's more than a color you
know like look at some of the Asians
look some of the the the Chinese the the
Koreans the Japanese they're very
they're physically whiter than white
people but somehow white people got the
title of white obviously you know when
you look at the other Asians that
they're not white you know for obvious
reasons because they're good at math you
know
so but even though white people got the
title of white like there's a lot of
people that are like look at the girl
behind you she's very light-skinned
right you're a lightskinned lady but I
could tell that you're not white but
white people wouldn't no you know what I
mean are you Pakistani I could tell
right away like you guys you guys gave
each other some sort of weird look
like I don't know some sort of weird
Pakistani [__] hand Cod
just but physically you're very fair
skinned you know what I mean like would
you have known uh Martin that that lady
wasn't white I mean obviously cuz here
but if we were somewhere else you might
have thought you know this is what
happens to like non-white people that
are very light-skinned we have this
identity crisis so we'll try to pass
ourselves not me but them they will um I
don't [__] pass off as anything um
you know other than you know what you
see um but you'll meet like people that
are very light-skinned and they'll pass
themselves off as white and the only
people that believe them are white
people the rest of us can see right
through them and like I'm like dude I
know you're not white how do you know
I'm not white don't I look white I go
you you're very fair skin but I know
you're not white well how do you know
I'm not white don't I look white I go
you look
pale but I know you're not how do you
know I'm not white cuz your [__] name
is ger
prit and when you're not actually white
like you're but you're just physically
white like you're not an actual white
person your body will remind you you
know what I mean like you sweetheart
you're very fair skinned right but I bet
you your nipples are chocy as [__] you
know what I mean like just you know what
I mean
like show me one real quick just one
just one it's it's not for me it's for
science it's for
science I don't want to see it like
sexually
just okay white lady there's a white
lady white lady show her one of yours
real quick just
show I want you to see what they look
like when they're raw this
is it's like uncooked white women have
nipple tartar it's amazing you got to
see this it's
okay take
me take me for example
right I'm a medium brown right there's
darker brown than me there's lighter
brown than me right but even though I'm
medium brown my junk black as [__] I
don't
understand I'm showering I'm
uncomfortable like who's is this
[Applause]
somebody just got the
joke backstage were like there might be
a a delay with the
translation I know the delay was going
to be [__] two days later I didn't
know that
I got kids I know you got kids team
teamour how many you got four
Jesus you're just like the Russians you
won't pull out of anything
um
uh okay your [__] is Ukraine
okay I will not pull out
[Laughter]
four from one
woman one woman nice congrats it's
honorable cuz I have four kids
um but I only made two of them I made
two and then my wife she has her own two
that she made before me because you know
she's a [__]
um kidding she's here babe I love you
don't leave me I don't know where they
put my wife but hopefully not near an ex
said bro
um I got uh I got two kids that I made
but um like I said Muhammad I grew up
with Jamaicans and um so I got some good
habits and some bad habits I got
rhythm but then I got bad habits you
know so I got two kids from two
different women thanks
Jamaicans and both of my kids are mixed
they're uh both my kids are half
Hispanic I don't know if there's any
Hispanic people here tonight Spanish
speaking you know
where are you guys from Mexico Mexico
what do you how the [__] did you end up
here how many walls did you want to hop
Jesus Christ I
mean Mir will hop a wall a wall and then
we'll end up with
h are you from Mexico W wo your wos are
from Mexico that's congrats on your wos
um
yeah I got two half Hispanic kids my but
when you have mixed kids I want you to
know something if you was your wife
Russian no what is she Ukraine that's
basically so I really wasn't wrong from
the beginning at all was
that baby this move is called chicken GI
that's not really I mean to you it's
mixed but not you know really my here's
here's the thing when you have mixed
kids you'll know this to be true oh
there's a couple right there I could see
that that's clearly not the same two
people um what where are you from Sir
South Africa South African you're
Filipino what are you Chinese Chinese oh
wow look at that who would have
thought and what's your name sweetheart
Christine Christine oh for sure
yeah now I looked at you I was like
that's [__] Christine for sure that's
where are your parents from Christine
Hong K Hong Kong oh yeah very it's a
very popular
name
Christine do you have a Chinese name as
well Christine what is
it was it M fin mof
fin isn't that they give you when you're
in the
hospital we have to give you
[Applause]
mine she's in so much
pain she need
mine and what's your family
name Wong so you're a Wong
mine we gave the one mine
that's a
lawsuit and is that your husband the
South African guy well you guys can't
stop colonizing either Jesus Christ
um do you guys have
babies one how old eight and a half
months eight and brand new
congratulations what did you what did
you name what boy or girl boy nice
that's good what did you name him did
you get a South African name or a
Chinese
name
Callum Callum you get him a [__]
thick ass Irish
name did you give him a Chinese name too
Christine so just basically [__] your
parents side is that what I like so when
he gets older people like Callum why are
you always
squinting I don't know
I have no [__]
clue Callum are you high what are you
talking
about I want to see your mom then you
can't meet
her there's my dad there's my
dad congrats on little
Callum
Callum when he gets older you'll notice
though uh depending on how you raise him
it's not even based on how you raise him
in fact um like I'll explain what I mean
like my my kids are both half half
they're mixed like my daughter she's 13
when your kids are mixed they can't be
both do you know what I mean like my
daughter's 13 now her mother's
Ecuadorian I'm Indian and I'm noticing
my daughter at 13 is leaning towards the
Indian side right and that's it's not a
victory trust me we don't uh the last
thing we need is more you know what I
mean
we I don't know if you know this
Christine but in April of 2023 India
passed China's population we have
finally [__] you
um it's really nothing to be proud of
the you know the Chinese are still way
more organized than the Indians will
ever be you could tell when you look at
the military the Chinese military is
all you look at the Indian
[Applause]
military we're never going to invade
anybody Pakistan you're safe we're never
going to show come on please just come
home come
home so my daughter 13 Ecuadorian and
Indian leaning towards the Indian side
now my son he's four and a half his
mother's Mexican and I'm noticing my son
at 4 and a half is leaning towards the
Mexican side and and uh that's fine with
me but I got to be honest with you it's
a lot more Mexican than I was prepared
for I didn't know you could be this
Mexican at 4 and a half when you're only
[__] 50% Mexican here's how Mexican
my son is um just laugh at this punch
line because I know you're not going to
get it anyway but the rest of the world
will so [__] you and laugh
okay um here's how Mexican my son is I
was with him the other day and I said
baby you want to go to Chuck-E-Cheese he
said Home Depot
I said wait you want to go inside Home
Depot
outside how does he
know you can't fight genetics my son is
Mexican as hell here's how Mexican my
son is uh what's your name Mexican guys
George Jorge jge Jorge and Javier Javier
Jorge and
jav here's how Mexican my son is like I
said live in Los Angeles I have a pool
in my backyard and I have a a fence
around my pool and
yeah he's halfway up the [__] thing
already
I I pulled him off you know what he
tried to do dig underneath I go what are
you
doing my little chaperito
and then my wife my wife is
Filipina and uh which is kind of awkward
walking around uh the UAE with a Indian
husband and a Filipino
wife everyone thinks the driver's
[__] The Nanny
[Applause]
um so my my wife is uh she's where's my
wife where are you babe where is she
she's out there right is she out there
do you know where she is she's over
there get a shot at her so they could
see that she's a real
person babe where are you stand up
hooker
um there she is that's her that's her
that's that's the one I
bought anyway my wife um is Filipina and
she has two daughters and uh those are
my daughters now cuz uh their dad wasn't
exactly active so I stepped in right I
mean he was active to make them but um
after that nah you know but uh so those
are my babies now those are my girls I
raised them those are uh but um I raise
them from 28 to 31 I
[Applause]
uh but my stepdaughters they're half
black and half Filipina so I got black
and filipin and Hispanic and Indian all
in one
house I should be getting a tax grant
for something I don't
know the only pure breeds in my house
are my
[Applause]
dogs Muhammad you'll appreciate this
since you're the since you're the only
closest thing to a black guy we have in
here right now um I'm the first and only
non black man my wife has ever been with
so
thanks those were some big penises to
fill those were
um the first time my wife and I did it I
was so scared I taped my balls to my
dick just so
it looked like a Pepsi can coming at her
just first time we did it and when I
tell you I fell in love I I fell in and
I
uh like a turtle on his
back we can't have stools like this in
my
house my wife's like
so
um baby where did that stool
go there it is
I'm kidding She's Tight She's Tight
um how old are your kids there Tim 11 6
4 and 3 months 11 six four and three
months wow space them out and then you
just rush the last few out nice congrats
and where's your wife I guess with the
three-month old back right now yeah
you're like you have the baby you stay
home did you come with Martin not come
with Martin cuz
obviously judging by your track record
if you did come with Martin he'd be
pregnant
um how old are you Timmy uh 39 39 God
damn 39 of four kids I'm 53 now that's
uh it's a no it's not it's nothing to
woo about it's uh getting old
how old are you so are you old or no 36
36 yeah no you're only two years older
than my
career that's not old to me that's that
was still the good old days for me
36 get older and young people bother you
you know like I used to think
Millennials were
[__] cuz I'm Gen X that's what I
guess my title would be Gen
X and then the Millennials came along
we're like [__] you Millennials the
Millen was like what's your problem dude
we're just the Next Generation why do
you got to be all old and you know you
don't understand and I'm like we
understand there's going to be somebody
to come along and [__] with you no there
won't we're going to be understanding
then j z show up and Millennial was like
what the [__] is their problem I'm
like it's inevitable as you get older
the Next Generation below you is going
to annoy you I remember when I was in my
early 20s a guy in his 50s came up to me
was like your generation sucks your
music is trash you haven't contributed
to this world I can't wait for life to
kick you in the nuts and I remember
looking at him and thinking in my head
[__] you you old
bastard you're just old and forgot how
to enjoy life when I get into my 50s
I'll never be like
you
Tada it's an evitable you don't want to
be like that but you just can't help it
you know I talked to Young you talked to
young people and you like
yeah have a young person talk to you
you're like just shut the [__]
up they want want to tell you things hey
did you know did you know did you know
did you know you could shut the [__] up
did you know
that did you know that in the 80s I was
there you're Googling my
life it's funny because like my
generation I'll admit this openly
that my generation is
unreasonably annoyed by gen Z and I'll
admit it to you and I know there's some
geny people here I could tell CU you're
all fidgeting like [__] crackheads
because you don't have your phones right
now you're
like I just need one Tick Tock
man let me just like a tick tock
man I got these
cheeseburgers that was for
scratch but everything that my
generation doesn't like about you young
people that kid who answers questions
and doesn't know he's answering
them what's your name Buddy what khed
hey
Khaled how how old are you khed 18 18
yeah you're exactly who I'm talking
about
[Applause]
yeah we're going to call you k khed
um I I feel bad cuz your mom's right
there but cuz every time I say something
your mom does this oh
yeah this is the one time your mom was
like I wish I wore the full I wish I
wore the full
[Applause]
but one day I should have wor
full I bring KH khed with
me kalet I'll tell you my generation is
mean to your
generation and I want to apologize but I
can't but it's true but here's the thing
everything my generation doesn't like
about your gener
is actually my generation's fault like
every single thing you guys do that we
don't like we made that happen like
think about what our generation says
about younger people they're [__]
lazy that's our fault because my
generation said you know what I'm going
to work hard so my kids don't have to
work that hard so they can enjoy life a
little bit
more but now we're mad at them for it
like why don't you get a job like got a
job I started a YouTube
channel I'm an
influencer what the [__] is an
influencer what do you do I open
packages and I film it and I tell people
what's inside the
package and I give them a review of the
package it's called an unboxing
and unbo that's the dumbest thing I've
ever heard in my life who watches this
[__] I have 5 million
subscribers influencer that's a real job
we didn't have any influencers in my
generation Salah did you know any
influencers growing up I knew I did I
knew one I knew one influencer it was um
my dad's right hand that was the only
influencer I knew
do the dishes I don't want to how about
I influence
you I'll open your head up like a
package I'll tell everybody what's
inside
[Applause]
nothing
unboxing My Generation box this
generation
unbox oh look
inside it comes in great packaging I
really like
it it's a nice weight it's got a good
weight to
it but everything they do that we don't
like we did this they're always on their
cell phone that's our fault we made the
cell phone they don't know what life is
like without the internet that's our
fault we made the internet inter they're
soft they never got beaten by their
parents we are their
parents it was our job to whoop their
asses and we failed and I know I'm
guilty of it cuz before I had kids I
talked all kinds of [__] I was like yo
you watch when I have kids I'm going to
[__] them
up what did I have first a daughter nope
never going to hit my
daughter 13 years old sweetest little
girl in the world I raised my voice at
my daughter I raised my voice on my
daughter once and then I cried right
after you know the worst part was she
consoled me she was it's okay Daddy
you're a nice
daddy but if you think about it every
generation's ass whoopings got less and
less and less to where it's at now I
remember my dad used to tell me how much
better my ass whoopings were than the
ones he got while he was whooping my
ass you're lucky this is all you're
getting you know your grandfather threw
a leopard at me what the
what where'd he get a leopard
from it was India they went
everywhere I like Dad I've been to India
20 times I never saw one leopard that's
because of your grandfather
everything that's wrong with this
generation is our
fault we did this to them but they took
it to another level you know we kind of
set it up and they just went extreme
with it you know like I'm from the
generation that makes fun of you when we
meet you my generation makes fun of you
we [__] with you and that's how we check
your temperature like if you can deal
with my [__] then we can be friends
you know what I mean but this younger
generation they do not get that at all
cuz they're so used to being fake like
everything about them is fake you don't
know how to be real anymore not you
maybe you do I don't know kid you don't
I can tell you don't because you raised
your hand then put it down when I asked
you like I didn't have hands you know
why not I'm
I but everything like like your
generation really doesn't understand the
ball breaking that's what we call it
khid we call it ball breaking that's
what guys do from my generation we break
balls and that's how we know we're okay
in America it's even worse like I I'll
give you an example I went to this uh
this uh store right I was buying a bunch
of stuff and I get to the cash to pay
for it and there's two young gen Z [__]
faces working there right a guy and a
girl maybe 20 21 years old right and um
the guy's ringing me up and the girl's
putting it in the bag and uh some guy
walks in to the store and the guy
ringing me up looks over and goes oh my
God I haven't worked with him in a while
and then the girl goes oh my God enus
and I go
what she goes that's his name enus and I
go what's his sister's name Aina
and and I started laughing right cuz cuz
it's [__] funny that's why I started
laughing but apparently I laughed like a
psychopath
a thinking that these kids are going to
go that's pretty funny too but they she
went he's really nice you
know I never said he wasn't nice I just
said his name's enus so you know it's
kind of kind of funny right and I'm
looking at the guy thinking the guy is
gonna you know be like oh yeah come on
he's pretty it's funny it's funny you
know like thinking he's going to go Guy
Code this little [__] nerd
looks at me goes you know he was bullied
a lot because of his
name I go
yeah he should have been his name is
[__]
enus you can't just go naming your kid
enus and think everything's going to be
okay there's no winning with this name
you're either penis or anus there's
nothing
[Applause]
good these kids just turn them here's
your your stuff sir thank you f very
much
[Music]
bye I don't want to be the person the
old guy that gets annoyed by young
people but you just do
it they're doing things to us you know
and at 53 you got to understand I'm
closer to
dementia than I am to anything else you
know and the way this generation's
behaving I'm going to think I have
dementia well before I have
dementia they're trying to get rid of
words this dude comes up and goes hey
man you can't say can't say the r word I
said I was in Japan neither can
they I go what our word by the way
Russell he goes no [__] go Who you
calling a
[__] no you can't say [__] anymore I
go I just
did I got bad news for you buddy I say
[__] all the time I say [__] I say
[__] I say [__] retardation I say
it
all and I feel
nothing well you're going to have to
stop I'm not going to stop saying [__]
until you get the French to stop saying
it I was at the airport in Canada and my
flight was
delayed and in English it said delayed
and in French it said on
[__] and I laughed like a little
school
girl I couldn't wait to call my friend
yo you're going to have to pick me up
later my flight's
[__] [__] in the UAE I bought
Ibuprofen that said Bruin
[__] it's literally in every drugstore
I bought it just to take home with me
anything to declare just this [__]
pills so yeah I'm not going to stop
saying [__] well you're going to have
to I said why why do I have to stop
saying [__] because it's offensive I
was like to
[Applause]
who you're the one calling people this
not me I'm calling everything but a
handicap person a [__] you call a
handicap person a [__] you're a piece
of
[__] and you can't say gay anymore what
I have gay friends I can't be like yo
these are my gay friends you you refer
to gay people as gay but you can't just
go arbitrarily calling things gay
anymore this is [__] [__] dude
this
is this is the gayest thing I've ever
heard in my life what do
you so wait I can't say gay or [__]
anymore no how am I supposed to talk to
my
brother every conversation is he call me
back you [__] don't be gay click
you got to understand I grew up in the
70s and 80s gay and [__] is always
said gay was the best insult you could
give a guy because it wasn't really
offensive it was more of a ah you got me
you know just you would never call
somebody gay if they were actually gay
but in the 70s we didn't realize gay was
a real thing like in the 70s like
nobody's really gay are they I
mean we just didn't know it was like a a
genetic we you know we didn't was
genetic we just like ah he's gay he's
not gay I mean who's really gay like you
know if you like if you like you know
but holes women have them too you know
what I mean like
just would have know was more than that
you
know and you would call somebody gay for
doing the most heterosexual thing
possible like like you Tim you have four
kids with your wife gay you know what I
mean like
that's CU it's the least gay thing you
could do
we were in denial in the 70s uh call it
if you want to have a good time you go
to YouTube and you type in uh the best
of the 1970s and you'll see right in
front of you that the 70s was the gayest
decade ever it was so and we had no clue
it was gay cuz we were in denial about
it I don't know if you guys remember the
Village
People the Village People they were like
the gayest group on the planet and we
had no clue they were gay like they're
not gay that guy's a construction worker
that guy's a biker that guy's Native
American they don't make gay Native
Americans they're singing about being a
macho man that's the least gay man you
can
be we didn't know what gay was I
remember in 1984 I'm in the mall I'm 14
years old one of my friends runs up me
goes yo come to the supermarket there's
two lesbians and I
ran because I'm 14 and I heard
lesbians what do I know about lesbians
at 14 nothing all I know is BL that's
all I
know that's it that's all that's it
that's all I
know and I'm like oh my God they must be
doing it in every aisle so I I run to
the supermarket I don't know what I'm
thinking like they're just hey let's go
to the mall and blah I don't know what
I'm I don't know what I'm
thinking I get to the supermarket I'm so
mad it was just two women with a
shopping cart
full of
[Applause]
cucumbers we didn't know anything in the
80s you
know that's why our generation's so
[__] up like that's why our generation
is created
genz we passed our [__] upness to the
next
Generations we skipped the Millennials
cuz that was a whole another
generation's
problem you know what it is like like
our gener My
Generation everything growing up
everything fell into this blanket of
life everything was called life there
was no subsections everything that
happened to you was life you lost your
job that's life my house burnt down man
that's life my wife left me that's life
bro everything was life there was
nothing to Define it other than life and
gen Z came along and wanted label
everything every [__] thing had a
label everything needed a
label and they ODed on the
label you know
like like I haven't always had add I
know I do but in the 80s there was no
diagnosis for the add I remember 1985 I
went to the guidance Council I go I was
15 I go what do you think's wrong with
me goes
H you're a [__] idiot
and I went is that like a
professional goes no no you're you're a
[__] idiot and I remember going that
sounds about fair I think yeah remember
going home my dad goes what did the
guidance counselor say said I was a
[__]
idiot he's
right like everything that we're
complaining about with jenzy is our
fault too like We complain that they're
sensitive you know every like everything
bothers them what's their problem why
are they so sensitive how come they get
so offended by everything every
interview I do is like Russell you
worried about cancel culture I'm like no
why not because the [__] these kids
aren't looking at me except for kak over
there
just but they get so they get offended
easy and that's and that's my
generation's fault too and I'll tell you
why it's our fault because my generation
started political correctness but here's
what young people don't understand we
started political correctness out of
necessity we didn't do it cuz we were
bored we did it because our parents
generation was
insane you got to understand my father
he was born in
1925 yeah my dad and my dad was here's
the thing my dad was born in India while
it was still under British
rule my dad was my dad said racist [__]
all day long he had no clue that it was
racist I go Dad you say a lot of racist
how can it be racist I learned English
from the
British they are the least racist
people we start a political correctness
because our parents generation didn't
know when not to say something it was a
Chinese family three houses down from me
my dad used to refer to them as the
Oriental
family I'm like Dad they're not
rugs from the age of four four or five
years old to now 53 97% of my friends
are black which is great but it was a
little awkward in my teenage years
because my dad used to use out ofd
terminology I remember being like 15 16
years old my friends would knock on the
door hi Mr Peters is russler here uh one
sec
uh please do me a fa go decide
just stay away from the
car
son there's a young negro boy here
looking for
[Applause]
you I come down my dad's pointing at
him I go Dad why are you pointing at him
so you know where he
is there's only one person standing
there no the Oriental boy is in the back
look see playing Chinese Chuckers or
something I don't know what he's doing
and I go to my dad this my this is what
was frustrating about my parents
generation they would defend everything
they said and their defense would make
sense I go Dad why did you call him a
young negro boy what part of that
description is not
correct is he an old white woman
no so we started political correctness
to stop that kind of stuff from going
forward we weren't trying to change the
world we were just trying to make little
differences so that there would be less
speed bumps for the next Generations we
meant well we were
naive then the Gen Z [__] faces showed
up and they took advantage of us and
they were like hey uh you know another
politically correct thing you guys are
doing I'm like yeah we'd like to add
some things to
it like oh sure we must have missed
something well well yeah would you like
to add um you know how I was born a
male
yeah yeah I'm I'm aware of that yeah I
don't feel comfortable identifying as a
male anymore
oh okay um well maybe you'd be more
comfortable identifying as a
female
[Music]
no those were the only
options I just feel like these are
social constructs that are designed to
keep us apart from each other when we
are neither black nor white not male nor
female we were simply just one people
one race the human race
and I'm like listen
here other
[__] I got real life adult problems
going on in my world I don't need your
young confused bored [__] to get in
my way now I want you to be whatever the
F you want to be and I want you to be
the best version of it you can be and
I'll support whatever it is you tell me
you think you are but you can't get mad
at me if I don't know what you think you
are when I look at
you if I see what I think as a dude I'll
like hey man I'm not a
man I identify as a
table how am I supposed to know you're a
table you only got two
legs you're a shitty
table I hear a lot of young people talk
about suffering from anxiety I I suffer
from
anxiety oh my God I'm suffering I see
you young girls you suffer from anxiety
don't you getting do you get anxiety I
know K do you get anxiety
no you sure buddy you're giving your mom
anxiety right now to be honest with
[Applause]
you young people my God I suffer from
anxiety look at me suffer [__]
anxiety how do you get anxiety in your
20s you got tax problems you got baby
mamas you don't have any [__]
anxiety young people have no clue what
anxiety is I know what anxiety is
because I dealt with it without even
knowing why I was dealing with it my
generation knows
anxiety let me tell you let me tell you
what real anxiety is let me tell you
what real anxiety is
anxiety this is what we had to deal with
anxiety was trying to masturbate to porn
in the
80s that's
anxiety cuz it's not like now where it's
just
everywhere anybody in this room don't do
it but anybody in this
room for no reason could pull out their
phone and look at porn just like that
just porn and then put it away I don't
know what you're thinking oh not over
here yeah everybody has a VPN you
[__] I know what you
do I'm I'm surprised Express VPN hasn't
opened up an office
here but porn is just there it's readily
available it's just it's it's just there
like back in the 80s it was not that
easy
it was a different time if you wanted to
see porn in the 80s you actually had to
be a real
pervert cuz you had to make a plan a
mental
plan not now you like I don't know I
think I might get a
boner back then you would plan it all
right
tonight I'm going to watch some porn
I know what you're thinking why couldn't
you just watch it any time because in
the 80s you only had one TV and one VCR
in the house and it was in the living
room
downstairs you couldn't just show up at
5:30 in the evening hey Mom Dad you
going to watch the news or can I
[Applause]
uh can I find out what Debbie's going to
do to
[Applause]
Dallas you to let make the plan and
here's what happened you would go to
bed and you would lay awake in your own
bed till like 2: in the morning wi awake
just you'd wait for everybody to go to
sleep that's how DED we
were you'd wait then you'd hear
everybody snoring you're like now
[Applause]
and you'd reach beside the bed where you
had the videotape cuz you stashed
it and you sneak out of your room you're
sneaking around your own
house like a perverted
burglar with an erection it's no good
[Applause]
just and you have these Miss in front of
you it's not as simple as just going
downstairs putting on the tape and Bam
you're good to go oh no no no that would
be too easy first you got to sneak
downstair first you got to wait then you
got to grab the tape now you got to
sneak downstairs but you can't walk down
the center of the stairs in case the
stairs
go so you're going to walk down the side
of the
stairs and now okay now you get
downstairs mission one
complete you got mission two in front of
you this is a big one you st staring at
a TV that's not even turned on yet
you're staring at it like Indiana Jones
you got this you're like sweating you're
like okay because what you got to do is
you got to turn the TV on this this is
the 80s you have to pull the knob on the
TV but at the same time that you pull
the knob you have to turn the volume
off so woo
did you know my generation didn't even
know that porno had
audio we had no
clue because you couldn't keep the
volume on you're the only thing awake at
this time of night you got to understand
my dad didn't just grow up in India my
dad grew up in the jungle in India my
dad had jungle ears he could hear [__]
we couldn't
here even if I put the volume on could
you imagine my dad sleeping and he just
hears what's that who's
that looks at my Mom that's not
you that's not
me it's
downstairs there's a leopard
[Applause]
so now you got the TV on volume off I
know what you're thinking kid porno time
no not even
close now you got the third mission you
got to get the videotape into the VCR
now here's what you need to understand
khid loading a VCR putting a videotape
in a VCR in a quiet house is easily one
of the loudest things you can do you
might as well just turn a blender on
just so what you got to do is you put
the video tape to the mouth of the VCR
then you grab a pillow off the
couch and you push the tape in with the
pillow because you need to smother the
[Music]
sound you're like shut the [__] up
and I know what you're thinking let the
porn begin no khid
no the movie doesn't just start like
that there's a test pattern that comes
on the screen and then the ever boner
killing FBI
warning now you're paranoid who's
watching
me and you don't even know about
tracking to you tracking is you say Nike
and all the ads in your Instagram come
up as Nike back in the day tracking was
the tape would start there'd be these
lines across the
screen and just a titty would be shaking
like this you're not even sure if it's a
tit like is that a a nipple or a hubcap
I can't tell is it a car or a boob I
don't know [__] it I'll take it you
don't know you just don't know
[Applause]
so now you got this shaking boob on your
screen like this and unless you're into
Parkinson's porn this is not going to
work for
you so now you got to walk over to the
VCR and there's a button called tracking
that you have to hit plus or minus or
wheel whatever you had until you got a
steady tit bam now you're good to
go you live in a very different time
like you can go to PornHub a 100,000
different times and in 100,000 different
times of going to Pornhub you may never
repeat the same scene that's how much
porn there is now back in the day we
looked at the same tape for four
years we had to act like it was new
every time you'd put it on you be like
hello Ginger Lin I haven't seen you in a
while
[Applause]
we had to
improvise PornHub ruined everything for
me let me tell you what PornHub is
here's what the problem with PornHub is
Pornhub took away all the mystery from
porn I know some of you are a little
uncomfortable right now just hearing
porn but it's not going to get graphic
don't
worry I know in your head you're going
this is Haram I don't want to hear it
um it's just the words it's nothing uh
graphic here I want the women to stay
with us on this one all right I
but porn here's what pornh Hub in like
back in the 70s and 80s porn movies had
titles and the titles were very subtle
you wouldn't even know it was a porn
that's how like here's a real porno
title from the 70s Behind the Green
Door what's Behind the Green Door I
don't know we better find
out porno movies had titles they were
shot on film you know where you had to
go to see a porno movie College back in
the 70s a movie theater
I wish there was some Babas in here who
could tell us that they
went I know if I was old enough in the
7s hell yeah I would have gone to a
porno movie theater would I have gotten
popcorn probably
not that's a commitment right there this
is salty I don't know what's wrong with
this
[Applause]
popcorn it's butter sticky
[Music]
the porno movies just have titles
original titles 7s and 80s original
titles 90s you know what they did in the
90s they got lazy in the 90s with porn
they uh they started taking real movie
titles and turning them into porno
titles so it' be like men in black
women
um Forest Hump uh pocah hot ass um
gindler fist
uh shaving Ryan's privates you know um
all the classics all the classics you
know then Along Came PornHub and just
ruined everything PornHub took the
mystery out of porn that's why I don't
like PornHub because just like all the
there's no there's no titles anymore
there's just there's no movies there's
just scenes and there's no titles
there's just explicit descriptions of
what you're about to see PornHub titles
remind me of white people's food let me
explain let's take Indian food for
example right so to make Indian food you
need a whole lot of different
ingredients and because we use so many
different ingredients we have to name
the dishes like what is that it's birani
what is that it's it's Rogan what is
that it's chicka Masala we give it names
because of all the ingredients white
people I'm not here to judge you but
you're very limited with your
ingredients to the point where you
literally name your food after the
ingredients what is that it's lemon
pepper
chicken what's in it
lemon
pepper and you guessed it
[Applause]
chicken oo what's that macaroni and
cheese what's in it
macaroni and cheese
o what's that fish and
chips what's in it what the [__] do you
think is in
it that's what PornHub titles are like
there's no mystery anymore you go to
PornHub just like hot Asian girl getting
destroyed by BBC you're
like God
damn and my mom walks in oh the BBC I
love the BBC I go no no no
this is not the BBC you're thinking of
keep it on I want to see the weather
that's not
precipitation they don't know the
struggle K you don't know what the
struggle was like in the
80s the 80s we had to improvise we get
we would try
anything these cataloges would come from
department stores they'd get mailed to
your house especially in North America
there was a store called
Sears they would mail a Sears catalog
and the catalog this is all before the
internet K the catalog would have all
the inventory from the store and there's
one book and they'd send it out every
season and you'd open the book and you'd
find what you wanted you make a little
Mark and you'd be like I'm going to go
to the store and I'm going to get this
right but if you were a perverted
teenager like I was in the 80s you would
go to the women's underwear department
in the book because it was the 80s there
was no
Photoshop so You' go to the women's bra
department and you'd look if it was a
lace bra you might see a nipple in the
back and then right
so or if you were a real perf like me
you'd go to the panties and you'd look
and there'd be like little hairs
creeping out the side
like but it was the 80s so you got to
understand like the women were natural
that back then big like big it was like
your hair ma'am
um it's you got a shot of that right
there we go yeah that right there yeah
yeah
it's like trying to put a mask on your
head you know what I mean
[Applause]
just K trophy hobbi
listen but that's what it was like in
the 80s women had a big old
Bush then the '90s they streamlined it
they made a little Landing
Strip 2000 they went
bald 2023
dick thank you very much you guys were
great
[Applause]
w
[Music]
oh e